export const QUESTION_ARRAY = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of the main character in 'The Witcher' series?",
        answers: ["Geralt of Rivia", "Ciri", "Yennefer", "Triss Merigold"],
        correctAnswer: "Geralt of Rivia"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Geralt's adopted daughter?",
        answers: ["Ciri", "Yennefer", "Triss Merigold", "Shani"],
        correctAnswer: "Ciri"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the secretive mountain fortress where Witchers are trained and mutated?",
        answers: ["Kaer Morhen", "Novigrad", "Vizima", "Beauclair"],
        correctAnswer: "Kaer Morhen"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the continent where most of the events in 'The Witcher' take place?",
        answers: ["The Continent", "Skellige", "Novigrad", "Toussaint"],
        correctAnswer: "The Continent"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the Emperor of Nilfgaard?",
        answers: ["Emhyr var Emreis", "Foltest", "Radovid V", "Eredin Br√©acc Glas"],
        correctAnswer: "Emhyr var Emreis"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the first short story collection by Andrzej Sapkowski, which introduced Geralt of Rivia?",
        answers: ["The Last Wish", "Blood of Elves", "Season of Storms", "Sword of Destiny"],
        correctAnswer: "The Last Wish"
    },
    {
        question: "What school does Geralt belong to?",
        answers: ["School of the Wolf", "School of the Viper", "School of the Bear", "School of the Griffin"],
        correctAnswer: "School of the Wolf"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the title of the bard who accompanies Geralt on his adventures?",
        answers: ["Dandelion", "Zoltan", "Roach", "Eskel"],
        correctAnswer: "Dandelion"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the ruler of the Kingdom of Redania during most of the events in 'The Witcher' series?",
        answers: ["Radovid V", "Emhyr var Emreis", "Foltest", "Henselt"],
        correctAnswer: "Radovid V"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the sorceress who holds a significant place in Geralt's heart?",
        answers: ["Triss", "Yennefer", "Fringilla Vigo", "Keira"],
        correctAnswer: "Yennefer"
    }
];
